[
    {
        "question": "When did cacti come to exist?",
        "expected": "35 million years BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When did Steller's sea cow become an extinct animal?",
        "expected": "1768, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When was Hachiko born?",
        "expected": "10 November 1923, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When did dodo's go extinct?",
        "expected": "1690, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When was the death of the last mammoth?",
        "expected": "18th century BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When is it believed that the first Koala existed?",
        "expected": "700000 years BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When did horses start being used for chariots?",
        "expected": "20. century BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When was the first crow sighting reported?",
        "expected": "17 million years BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When did Mammoths go extinct?",
        "expected": "18. century BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When was the first blue whale born?",
        "expected": "1500000 years BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Since when do Platypuses exist?",
        "expected": "9 million years BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "How heavy is a jaguar when born?",
        "expected": "800 plus or minus 100 gram, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When were cats first domesticated?",
        "expected": "518 BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Since approximately when has the process of horse domestication started?",
        "expected": "25th century BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When did the dodo go extinct?",
        "expected": "1690, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When was the human with highest recorded livespan born?",
        "expected": "21 February 1875, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When did the cucumber receive the award for vegetable of the year?",
        "expected": "2019, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When did velociraptors go extinct?",
        "expected": "71 million years BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When was nettle awarded medicinal plant of the year?",
        "expected": "1996, 2022, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When was there the first animal on earth?",
        "expected": "665 million years BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When did dodos go extinct?",
        "expected": "1690, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When did Unsinkable Sam die?",
        "expected": "1955, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When did we start cultivating cucumbers?",
        "expected": "Circa 3000 BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When did the tomato plant win 'Vegetable of the year' award?",
        "expected": "2001, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When did bats first appear?",
        "expected": "52 million years BCE, "
    },
    {
        "question": "When was sunflower oil invented?",
        "expected": "1829, "
    },
    {
        "question": "Since when have isopoda been around?",
        "expected": "300 million years BCE, "
    }
]